A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1952-1966 (bulk 1958-1965)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1956-1966., Extent: 30.8 cu. ft. (Box 1-81d)
  - Centennial Commissions.
    - United States (National Commission): Newsletters, 1958-1961. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - United States (National Commission): Newsletters, 1962-1965. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Vermont, 1960. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - West Virginia, 1959-1960. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - West Virginia, 1961-1962. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - West Virginia, 1963-1964. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Wisconsin, 1959-1964. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Commemorations.
    - Appomattox, 1964-1965. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Appomattox, 1965. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Appomattox, 1965. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Appomattox: Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1965. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Appomattox: Newspaper Clippings, 1965. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Appomattox: Records and Reports, 1965; undated. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Appomattox: Sound and Light, 1964-1965. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox: Sound and Light, (Newspaper Clippings), 1964-1965. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Confederate States Battlefield Memorial, 1962-1965. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Chambers, Lenoir, ("The Whole Jackson" address), 1963. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Jefferson, (Inauguration), 1961-1962. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Jefferson, (Inauguration), undated. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Jefferson, (Postage Stamp), 1959-1961. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - General, The, (Steam Locomotive), 1962-1963. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Hunley (Submarine), 1962-1963. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Kirkland, Richard, Monument, 1961-1965. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Kirkland, Richard, Monument, (Newspaper Clippings), 1963-1965. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Manassas, 1959-1964. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Manassas: Gun Carriages, 1962-1963. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Monitor and Merrimack Electric Diorama, 1960-1963. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Monitor and Merrimack Electric Diorama: Clippings and Supporting Documentation, 1961-1963. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Parades and Bands, 1959-1962. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Correspondence, 1959. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Correspondence, 1960. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Correspondence, 1960. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Correspondence, 1961. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Peace Convention (1861): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Correspondence, 1962. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Newspaper Clippings, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Rededication of Virginia's Gettysburg Monument: Newspaper Clippings, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Stonewall Jackson, 1962-1963. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Stonewall Jackson Dinner: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Stonewall Jackson Dinner: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Stonewall Jackson Dinner: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1963. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Stonewall Jackson Dinner: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1963. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Stonewall Jackson Symposium, 1961-1962. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Stuart's Ride around McClellan: Correspondence, 1961-1962. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Stuart's Ride around McClellan: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1961-1962. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Submarines: Robert E. Lee and Stonewall Jackson, 1963-1965. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Taps Commemoration, 1962. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Construction of Centennial Center.
    - Bid Information, 1960. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Changes in Plans, 1960. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Changes in Plans, 1961. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Changes in Plans, 1961. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Changes in Plans, 1961. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Changes in Plans, 1962. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Clerk of the Works: Weekly Reports, 1960-1961. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1960. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1960. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1960. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1960. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1961. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1961. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1961. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Building Sites, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Proposed Building Sites, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Proposed Building Sites, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Sewer Relocation, 1960. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Shop Drawings (Correspondence), 1960. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Telephone Service, 1960. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence.
    - Authenticity, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Emblems and Markers, 1959-1962. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Coins, Confederate Money and Medals, 1959-1961. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Exhibits: Books, Music and Poetry, 1961. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Exhibits: Books, Music and Poetry, 1962. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Exhibits: General, 1959-1960. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Exhibits: General, 1961-1964. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Exhibits: Grave Markers, 1959-1963. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Exhibits: Guns, 1959-1960. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Exhibits: Photographs and Prints Available, 1960-1964. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Exhibits: Stonewall Jackson, 1962-1963. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - General, 1963-1964. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - General, 1965. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - General, 1965. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - General, 1966. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Maps and Highway Markers, 1959. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Maps and Highway Markers, 1960. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Maps and Highway Markers, 1960. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Maps and Highway Markers, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Maps and Highway Markers, 1962-1965; undated. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Museums: Civil War Hall of Fame, 1960-1961. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Museums: Lee Chapel, 1963-1964. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee.
    - Member Correspondence: Abbitt - Baldwin, 1958-1965. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Member Correspondence: Barringer, 1958-1966. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Member Correspondence: Bean, 1958-1965. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Member Correspondence: Carter, 1959-1964. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Member Correspondence: Cooke, 1958-1961. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Member Correspondence: Cooke, 1962-1965. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Member Correspondence: Hoover - Moncure, 1958-1960. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Member Correspondence: Moses, 1958-1965. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Member Correspondence: Owens - Unruh, 1959-1965. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Memorandums and Supporting Documentation: Executive Director, James G. Geary, 1960-1963. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Memorandums and Supporting Documentation: Executive Director, James G. Geary, 1964-1965. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Minute Record, 1958-1965. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Minutes and Supporting Documentation, 1962-1963. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Minutes and Supporting Documentation, 1964. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Minutes and Supporting Documentation, 1965. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Films.
    - Another Cheer for Dixie: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Another Cheer for Dixie: Correspondence, 1965. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Another Cheer for Dixie: Correspondence, 1965. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Another Cheer for Dixie: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1964-1965. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Another Cheer for Dixie: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1964-1965. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Another Cheer for Dixie: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1964-1965. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Center: Correspondence, 1959-1960. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Center: Correspondence, 1961-1962. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Center: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1959-1961. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Center: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1959-1961. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Character of Lee: Correspondence, 1960-1962. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Character of Lee: Correspondence, 1963-1965. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Character of Lee: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1962-1965. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - General, 1963-1966. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Manassas to Appomattox: Copyright, 1961-1963. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Manassas to Appomattox: Correspondence, 1962-1965. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Manassas to Appomattox: Miscellaneous Documentation, undated. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Requests for Films after Closing of Center, 1965-1966. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1962-1963. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1965. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Correspondence, 1965. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1963. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1964-1965; undated. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Miscellaneous Documentation, undated. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Television Showings, 1963. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Stonewall Jackson's Way: Television Showings, 1963. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Finances.
    - Appropriation Allotments, 1958-1962. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Business Manager: Correspondence, 1959-1963. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1959. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1960. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1961. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1962-1965. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Budget Requests, 1960-1966. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Contracts: A - C, 1961-1962. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Contracts: D, 1959-1963. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Contracts: E, 1961. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Contracts: F, 1961-1962. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Contracts: I, 1961-1962. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Contracts: L, 1959-1961. (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Contracts: M, 1959-1965. (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Contracts: P - R, 1960-1965. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Contracts: S, 1960-1962. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Contracts: T, 1960-1962. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Contracts: W, 1961-1963. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Copyright, 1961. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1960. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1961. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1961. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1963. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Equipment Records, 1958-1965. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Equipment Records, 1958-1965. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Financial Statements, 1958-1965. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Insurance, 1960-1961. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Ledger Sheets: Expenditures, 1958-1961. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Lee Papers, 1959-1960. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Memorandums, 1960-1961. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Office Space: Leasing of, 1958-1961. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Publications: Orders for, 1960-1962. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Publications: Orders for, 1962-1964. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Publications: Sales of, 1961-1962. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Revenue, 1961-1962. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Local Centennial Committees.
    - Accomack, 1959-1961. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Alexandria, 1959-1960. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Alexandria, 1961. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Alexandria, 1962-1965. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Alleghany - Amherst, 1959-1964. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Appomattox, 1959-1964. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Arlington, 1959-1965. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Augusta - Bath, 1959-1964. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Bedford, 1960-1964. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Bland - Buchanan, 1959-1961. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Buckingham, 1960-1964. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Bristol - Carroll, 1959-1963. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Charles City - Charlotte, 1959-1962. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Charlottesville, 1959-1963. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake (formerly Portsmouth and Norfolk), 1959-1965. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Chesterfield - Clarke, 1959-1964. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Clifton Forge, 1961-1963. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Colonial Heights - Craig, 1959-1963. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Culpeper - Cumberland, 1959-1963. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Danville - Dickenson, 1959-1965. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Dinwiddie, 1959-1960. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Dinwiddie, 1961-1966. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Essex, 1959-1961. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax, 1959-1960. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax, 1961-1963. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Falls Church - Fauquier, 1959-1961. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Fluvanna, 1959-1963. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Franklin - Frederick, 1960-1962. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Fredericksburg, 1959-1961. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Fredericksburg, 1962-1965. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Fredericksburg: Newspaper Clippings, 1961-1963. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Fredericksburg Area - Gloucester, 1959-1965. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Goochland - Greensville, 1959-1965. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Halifax - Hanover, 1959-1965. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Harrisonburg, 1959-1961. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Harrisonburg, 1962-1965. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Harrisonburg: Newspaper Clippings, 1962. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Harrisonburg: Newspaper Clippings, 1962-1965. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Henry - Hopewell, 1959-1966. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Henrico, 1959. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Henrico, 1960. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Henrico, 1961. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Henrico, 1962-1965. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Isle of Wight - Lancaster, 1959-1964. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Loudoun, 1960-1962. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Louisa - Lynchburg, 1959-1965. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Martinsville - Madison, 1959-1962. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Mecklenburg - Nansemond, 1959-1965. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Nelson - New Kent, 1959-1965. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Newport News, 1959-1965. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk - Northampton, 1959-1962. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Northumberland - Nottoway, 1959-1965. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Orange - Page, 1959-1961. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Patrick, 1960-1964. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Peninsula Committee, 1959-1960. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Petersburg, 1959-1965. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Pittsylvania - Prince George, 1959-1964. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Prince William - Radford, 1959-1962. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Rappahannock - Rockbridge, 1959-1963. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Rockingham - Scott, 1959-1962. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Shenandoah County, 1959-1965. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Shenandoah Valley, 1959-1961. (Box 48, Folder F6)
    - Shenandoah Valley, 1961-1963. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Letters of Appreciation, 1961. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Membership Certificates, 1960-1962. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Reports on Centennial Publications, 1965-1966. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Tax Exemptions, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters.
    - Volume 1, Numbers 1-12, 1959-1960. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Volume 2, Numbers 1-12, 1960-1961. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Volume 3, Numbers 1-6, 8-12, 1961-1962. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Volume 4, Numbers 1-12, 1962-1963. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Volume 5, Numbers 1-12, 1963-1964. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Volume 6, Numbers 1-12, 1964-1965. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Volume 7, Numbers 1-3, 1965. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Operations.
    - Emancipation Proclamation, undated. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Grass Roots Ideas, 1960. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Grass Roots Microfilming, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Grass Roots Organization, 1959-1960. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Legislation, 1961-1963. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Libraries, 1959-1960. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Libraries, 1961-1963. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Play Committee, 1962-1963. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Requests for Speakers, 1960. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Requests for Speakers, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Speakers, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Regional Assembly: Roanoke, 1962-1963. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Speakers Bureau: Correspondence, 1960-1962. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Speakers Bureau: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Statewide Assembly (First): Correspondence, 1960. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Statewide Assembly (First): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Statewide Assembly (Second): Correspondence, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Statewide Assembly (Second): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Statwide Assembly (Second): RSVPs, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Statewide Assembly (Third), 1961-1962. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Statewide Assembly: Fredericksburg, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Statewide Assembly: Fredericksburg, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Training Program, 1961. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Files.
    - Advertising and Markers, 1963-1964. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Appomattox, undated. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Art Work, undated. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Center, undated. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Center, undated. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Centennial Center, undated. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Center, undated. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Center, undated. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Centennial Opening Day Ceremonies, 1961. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Fort Monroe, undated. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Gettysburg Rededication (possibly), undated. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Lee Chapel, Lexington, Virginia (Recumbent Statue of Lee), undated. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Mariners Museum, Civil War Wing Models of Ironclads, undated. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Petersburg National Military Parks, Cannon at Fort Stedman undated. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Richmond National Battlefield Park Headquarters, Chimborazo Park, undated. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Statues and Memorials, undated. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Statues and Memorials, undated. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Statues and Memorials, undated. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Statues and Memorials, undated. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Images, undated. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Projects.
    - Appomattox Centennial Plans: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Appomattox Centennial Plans: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Appomattox Centennial Plans: Correspondence, 1965. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Appomattox Centennial Plans: Invitations, 1964-1965. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox Centennial Plans: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1964-1965. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Barbee Confederate Statue, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Bethel Marker, 1963-1964. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Boy Scout Camporee, 1961-1962. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Center Film Script, 1961. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Commission Exhibit at the Virginia Educational Association Convention, 1963-1964. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Confederate Medical Exhibit at the Richmond Academy of Medicine: Correspondence, 1958-1960. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Confederate Medical Exhibit at the Richmond Academy of Medicine: Correspondence, 1961-1965. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Confederate Medical Exhibit at the Richmond Academy of Medicine: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1958-1961. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Films: Stonewall Jackson's Way Participants 1962-1963. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Films: Stonewall Jackson's Way Props, 1962-1963. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Flag Day: Correspondence, 1962-1963. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Flag Day: Miscellaneous, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Historical (1962-1963 Biennium): Correspondence, 1961-1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Historical (1962-1963 Biennium): Miscellaneous Documentation, 1963-1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Huguenot Springs Cemetery, 1962-1963. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - "J.E.B. Stuart: Calvary Leader," 1963-1964. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Manassas Reenactment: Correspondence, 1959. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Manassas Reenactment: Correspondence, 1960. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Manassas Reenactment: Correspondence, 1960. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Manassas Reenactment: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Manassas Reenactment: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1959-1961. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Manassas Reenactment: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1959-1961. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Music: Correspondence, 1960. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Music: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Music: Correspondence, 1962-1963. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Music: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1961; undated. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Notes for CSA Rosters, undated. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Notes for CSA Rosters, undated. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Notes for CSA Rosters, undated. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Notes for CSA Rosters, undated. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Notes for CSA Rosters, undated. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Oaths of Allegiance (photostats), 1865. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Opening Day: Correspondence, 1960-1961. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Opening Day: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Opening Day: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Opening Day Parade: Correspondence, 1959-1961. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Opening Day Parade: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1961. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Opening Day Parade: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1961. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Plays: Correspondence, 1960. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Plays: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Plays: Correspondence, 1962. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Plays: Correspondence, 1963-1964. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Plays: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961; undated. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Plays/Drama: Correspondence, 1959. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Plays/Drama: Correspondence, 1960. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Plays/Drama: Correspondence, 1961-1963. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Plays/Drama: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1959-1962. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Plays Returned, 1961-1962. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Robert E. Lee, 1953-1961. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Search for Civil War Documents: Correspondence, 1961-1962. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Search for Civil War Documents: Correspondence, 1963. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Search for Civil War Documents: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1962-1963. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Search for Civil War Documents: Miscellaneous Documentation, undated. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Shenandoah Apple Blossom: Correspondence, 1959-1964. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Shenandoah Apple Blossom: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Correspondence, 1962-1963. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Correspondence, 1964. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Correspondence, 1964-1965. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1965; undated. (Box 58, Folder 6)